Priya , where 's my blade ?
Must be near the sink . - Okay .
I am putting the clothes in the machine .
Divya , wash the white ones separately .
Or else they will get coloured as well . - Okay .
Put my clothes in too , Aunt . - Fine , put them in .
Deepa . I 'm getting late . Quickly get me tea .
Right away . Just a second .
Priya , please give Manoj tea . I have to get the children ready . - Okay .
Riya , quickly drink your milk . You 'll miss your school bus .
Divya . Divya . - Yes .
Have this kept in the prayer room . - Okay .
The milk has curdled again . It 's just too much .
Good morning , brother . - Morning .
How was your first night in the new house ? .
Like always . - Really . You seem to be experienced about first nights .
Of course . I have two children .
Wait to go , brother .
Fetch it quickly . I am getting late .
Mannu , please check the cable connection before leaving for office .
We couldn 't watch our serial yesterday .
Gas , electricity , water .. they aren 't worried about these things .
But they create a stir for no cable connection .
Mom , the serial starts at 1 o 'clock .
Why are you whining already ? .
What ? . I couldn 't hear anything .
Mummy , your son is mocking our serial .
Okay . Brother , hold on . - What happened ? .
What 's wrong with the tea ? . It tastes different .
I 've used milk powder . The milk curdled again .
Try to adjust today . - The milk curdled again .
Yes . - It 's not a good omen .
What 's wrong ? . - The milk curdled yesterday .
And today as well . That 's not a good omen at all .
Mom . Mom , sit . Take a seat . - Sit .
Sit , let me explain it to you . - But you know , it 's ..
Sit , let me explain it to you .
Look , brother and I used all of our savings to buy this flat . - Yes .
Now , this flat won 't be ours ..
.. until we don 't repay the loan in the next 20 years .
So , forget all the bad omens .
Because we are going to live in this house happily ..
.. for the next 20 years . - Yes .
Brother , please tell her . - Of course .
Uncle . - Young man , that 's not a toy .
Your uncle had to pay a lot of money to buy this .
Go to school . Come on , go . - Come on . Get ready quickly .
We are getting late . - Have your breakfast .
The children these days go straight for the mobile phones .
You will get late for school . - Mom , last cartoon .
Don 't watch so much T.V. , or else you will have to wear spectacles .
Grandma , aunt and you watch T.V. the entire day .
You never had to wear spectacles .
Quiet . You have started back-answering ..
.. since you started going to school .
Come on , eat .
Come on . Let 's go to school .
Brother , talk to him . - I tried to , but he never listens .
Mother , we are getting late .
I 'll take them to their pickup spot . - Okay . - Come on , let 's leave .
Bye . Bye . - Bye . All the best . - Bye , mom .
Brother , don 't forget me . - I thought you forgot about it .
Anyway . - What ? .
Be back before 6 o 'clock in the evening .
Yeah , I will be back . Bye , Mom . Bye , everyone . - Bye .
Have your breakfast . - I 'll have it at college .
This girl never eats anything .
Mannu . - What is it ? .
You still haven 't put up the pictures in the prayer room .
Sorry , brother . I didn 't get the time yesterday .
I will certainly get it done today .
Promise . - Promise .
Don 't forget to do it by evening .
Okay , Mom . I 'm leaving . - Okay , son . Bye .
I am getting late as well . I 'm leaving .
We 'll meet in the evening . - Bye .
Fine , Mom . - Bye .
See you , mother . - Bye , dear .
Mom , I am leaving . - Fine .
Mom , I am leaving - Go .
Mom , I am leaving . - Why are you blowing at my ears ? .
If you want to say goodbye to Priya , then go inside .
She 's taking a bath . - No Mom , I meant you . Fool .
Strange .
Sir . Sir , your dog ! - No .
Come back . Harry , no . Down , boy .
Down , boy . - Sir , please . Keep your dog away .
Who is it ? . - Sir , my name is Manohar .
And I recently shifted to flat number 1 3B .
Oh , hello . My name is Kaamdar .
The watchman was just talking about your family . - Really !
For the past two weeks your carpenters ..
.. were creating quite a racket . - I am really sorry .
I tried to tell them . But you know how these people are .
No problem . Actually , it 's a new building .
No one has the right to complain .
But yes , I do . The Lord took away my sight .
But I still have ears to listen .
But if you keep making such noise ..
.. I will have to use earplugs .
I am so sorry .
By the way , I am getting late . Can I leave ? .
Sir , next Friday I have a holiday .
If you wish , you can have lunch with me and my family .
What do you say ? .
Sure . Why not ? . I will surely come .
See you , bye . Bye , Harry . - Bye .
Mr. Manohar . - Yes .
Will you walk down 1 3 floors ? .
There 's a lift . Let 's use that .
Actually , the lift is not working .
I thought I 'd tell the watchman on my way out .
Oh , fine .
Come , Harry .
Stupid lift .
Watchman !
You called , sir . - Slowly , man . Not so hard .
Do you know my flat , 1 3B ? . - Yes , sir .
Just go there between 1 pm to 1 : 30pm ..
.. put up a few pictures in the prayer room ..
Fine , sir . - Here , keep this .
Listen , don 't go there between 1 pm to 1 : 30pm . Go after that .
They will be watching TV , and will kill you . - Fine , sir .
Okay , I am leaving . - Okay .
Watchman . - Sir .
The lift of our building is not working properly . - Yes , sir .
Call the service company and ask them to repair it . - Fine , sir .
I will get it done . Okay .
I am leaving . - Okay . - Okay , sir .
Good morning , sir . - Morning .
He will get you out .
Morning , sir . - Morning .
Hey , what 's up ? . - Morning , sir .
Has the concrete arrived ? . - Forget the concrete .
Tell me about your new house .
The house is simply amazing . - Is it ? .
When I open the window of my flat on the 1 3th floor ..
.. it feels like Manhattan . - Very good .
And the cross ventilation is simply outstanding . - Really .
Just a minute . - Hello .
I don 't need any loan . I am already in debt .
Pestering people . I think the ad agency gets our number ..
.. before we do .
New phone , new house . You are on a roll . - Listen .
I got it on discount . It 's a very cheap phone . - Liar .
What 's wrong ? .
Get it changed from wherever you bought it .
There 's a problem with the lens .
It was fine this morning .
Smile . You are looking handsome .
Alright . - I think Gulabi will be floored . - Of course .
There 's no problem with the phone .
My 7-year-old nephew took that picture .
He must have shaken the mobile . Get that .
Are all the workers present ? . - Yes , sir .
Tell me , Laxmi . If he 's not my child , then whose is it ? .
What can I say ? . - Laxmi , say something .
They always end it so abruptly .
Laxmi didn 't get a chance to tell him the truth ..
.. and they ended the programme .
Mummy , you watch the programme so seriously .
You should start writing one .
Our TV programme will be a hit , right ? . - Quiet .
You are just .. Mummy , sister-in-law is right .
Priya , ' Shubh Vivaah ' will start now .
Bring the remote quickly . Change the channel .
Hurry up .
Mummy , tell me what happened last week .
Last week .. The door bell rung and Mandira opened the door .
The music was so scary ..
Mummy , there 's no one .
Must be the gas cylinder guy .
Change it . - Press it .
Come on . - What 's wrong ? . - I cannot change it .
Just a minute . I 'll try it .
You will make me miss ' Shubh Vivaah ' .
The battery must be dead . Change it from the panel .
Hurry up . It 's time for the serial to start .
Mummy , I cannot change the channel .
Is something wrong with the T.V. ? . - I don 't know .
What 's this ? . - Seems to be a new serial .
New serial . New house and new serial .
" Fine ! Everything is fine ! "
And anyway , ' Shubh Vivaah ' had become very boring .
" Everything is fine . "
Look , Mother . After all the tribulations and difficulties ..
.. our house looks so wonderful .
It really is beautiful . But son ..
.. did we need to pay such a big price for it ? .
Mother , your happiness is priceless to us .
Brother and I have taken a loan .
And Mother , we will repay this loan soon enough .
Watchman .
Oh God , what a punishment .
What 's wrong ? . Why are you gasping ? .
You don 't know . I had to climb up 1 3 floors .
I told the watchman that the lift is not working .
But he didn 't do anything about it .
Give it to me . - Thanks .
Oh God . - What ? .
You still haven 't put up the pictures . - What can I do ? .
I gave Rs.50 to that watchman for putting them up . Didn 't he come ? .
He did , and also tried . But he couldn 't bore the nails in .
I think there 's a beam here . - What ? .
As an engineer 's wife , you know everything .
There 's a beam through the entire room . - Could be .
Okay , do one thing . Get me a hammer . I will do it .
Before brother arrives and hammers me .
Fine .
Only after her family ran into trouble , did she realise it .
Now she 'll realise there 's a delay , but not denial .
She 'll know it now .
Who ? . - I always said so , but you never believed me .
Did you see that now ? . - Listen . What is mom gossiping about ? .
About the daily soap operas .
Oh God . - She couldn 't see today 's episode . She missed it .
So , she 's asking aunt Kamla about it .
You and your serials .
You 've been watching the same TV programme for many years .
The same story . Doesn 't it make any difference to you ? .
Darling , why don 't you watch some episodes ? .
And then we can discuss them .
Forget it . - Don 't mock me .
Faces change .
She joins in again .
Look at her role ..
Just a minute . Mannu , why are you creating a racket ? .
Do it slowly . I am talking on the phone .
Yes , Kamla .
Mannu , didn 't you hear ? .
Oh God . Damn it !
What happened ? . You are just ..
What do you think ? . I am hurt . Get some ice . - I 'll get it right away .
Mummy , see what happened . - What happened ? . What happened ? .
I got hurt . - What was the need ? .
You came home late from work . You should be resting ..
And you are doing this . - What a wonderful mother . Don 't be silly .
No , nothing . - Mannu , you .. Here , keep this .
God . - It must be really painful .
It 's the 21st Manohar . Remember to pay the flat maintenance fee .
That 's all . What 's this ? . Lower your feet .
Come on , your mummy is waiting with the milk . - Papa , Papa .
And you all are just .. Papa , Papa .
Brother , the milk has curdled again .
Since we arrived in this house , I haven 't had a descent cup of tea .
This has become daily routine now . - Forget it .
Hello , good morning . Welcome to ' Hum Se Door . '
Just a minute . Go back . - Have you seen a ghost ? .
That 's Dr. Shinde . - Right .
Call mother . - There are many people who .. - Mother , look who 's on T.V.
.. who 's seen a ghost . - Who is it ? . - Your boyfriend .
Most of the people .. - What ? . - What are you doing ? .
What are you saying ? .
Many of them are enemies of human beings .
Hey . - Yes , right . - That 's the doctor .
Let me sit . What 's he telling ? .
Oh God , such enthusiasm . - Let me sit .
Everything is a joke for you .
That 's right .
You know , I am sitting here hale and hearty because of him .
Or else I would have been dead by now .
Mother , don 't say such things .
You know , we consulted so many doctors .
But he was the only one who diagnosed my problem .
So , why are you getting so emotional ? .
Come , let 's .. - Be quiet . Let me hear .
Doctor . - Hello . - You are considered ..
.. to be one of the best general practitioners in India .
But why are you on the discussion panels for paranormal behaviour ? .
I was very young when my parents passed away .
I had a younger brother . I brought him up like my own child .
But he passed away in an accident .
I wanted to tell my brother how much I love him .
As a doctor , we try to save a human being as long as he isn 't dead .
We try our best to save his life , but if they still die ..
But what after death ? .
What happened to all those dead people ? .
Where are they ? .
I got interested in this subject while looking for these answers .
8 : 30pm . Always late . - Raghav , where were you ? . Sit here . - Okay .
Priya , bring Raghav 's breakfast . - Yes , sister-in-law .
Are ghosts , spirits and the after-life , really true ? .
Or is it just superstition ? .
Take Newton 's third law . ' Every Force has an equal and opposite force . '
Similarly , in spirituality .. if there are Gods and temples ..
.. then it 's necessary to have an opposite force as well .
Look . - Smile , aunt . - Here 's your breakfast .
Smile , Aunt .
Divya , eat up . - Aunt .
Uncle 's mobile . He will scold you today . It 'll be fun .
Go and return it to uncle . - Run quickly .
And if there 's life , there 's after-life as well .
And if there are Gods and temples ..
.. there must be a world of spirits as well .
But that 's my own opinion . Everyone doesn 't have to believe it .
Uncle .
Dennis the Menace , I told you this is not a toy .
I will get you a toy in the evening if you want one . - Okay .
Go . You are getting late for school . - Go on .
How many times have I told you ..
.. to keep the phone out of the children 's reach ? .
I do , but he always finds it .. strange .. - You are too much ..
Mom , just a minute . - Please , don 't take my photograph .
How many times have I asked you not to ? . ! Please don 't do it .
He 's a famous personality .
New issue .. what is your opinion about our show .
Mother , it 's getting late . I am leaving . - Fine . - Bye .
Bye . - Mannu . - Yes .
Remember to send the driller home ..
.. to put up the photos in the prayer room . - Fine .
Don 't forget . - I won 't , brother .
Stupid lift .
Is the driller free ? . - Why ? .
Call him . I have some work .
The driller must be .. Hari . - Yes , sir .
Hari , do you know about my new flat ? .
Yes , I know . - I have some work .
Take a taxi . And finish the work .
Good day . - Yes .
I am the driller , ma 'am . I am coming from the site .
Mr. Manohar has sent me . - Okay , come in .
Come . Here it is .
I 've made the marks . You just have to bore in the nails . - Fine .
Get it done . - Yes , madam .
Would you like to have tea or coffee ? . - No . - Okay .
Who is it , Priya ? . - It 's the driller .
I have shown him the prayer room , Mummy .
Mummy .
Oh God .
Brother . Brother .. Are you fine ? . Are you fine ? .
Hey , what happened ? .
Go .. Go .. Call the ambulance . - Yes .
Brother . Brother .
Brother , get up .
Are you fine ? . Are you fine ? .
Shall we call the doctor ? . - No .
Don 't call the ambulance .
Come . Rest by the wall . Come on .
Be careful while working .
What if something had happened to you ? .
Oh God .
I have been doing this work for many years now .
I have suffered from many surprises many times .
But nothing so intense .
It seems like industrial power . - What ? .
But , we ..
Please get the wiring checked after sir arrives . - Fine .
There are children in this house . It 's better to be careful . - Yes .
My drill machine . - Yes , here it is .
Here .
I am not feeling fine . I will do this work later .
Absolutely . Tomorrow or the day after , whenever you feel fine .
But please leave now , get a check up and go home and rest .
Take care and rest .
I was so scared . The way he screamed ..
And there was froth coming from his mouth .
I didn 't know what happened . - I was so scared .
They don 't work carefully .
There 's something wrong in this house .
Since we arrived , something bad is constantly occurring .
The milk curdles everyday . The prayer room is not ready .
Why do I always feel there 's something in this house ..
.. other than my family ? .
Ghosts and spirits , ghouls . Or someone 's soul .
I don 't know . But I cannot talk to anyone about it .
If I mention this to mother , she will be obstinate ..
.. about vacating this house .
If brother finds out , he will arrange for venerations and prayers .
I am scared that something bad is going to happen in this house .
Mohan ! Mohan , my brother .
Why are you so late ? . And these sweets ? .
First , open your mouth . - But what is the ..
Open your mouth . - What 's the matter ? . - I have been promoted .
Wow . Great news . - Let me share the entire news .
Tell me . - I got a salary hike of 1 0,000 a month .
1 0,000 a month . Wow .
The loan period for this house is 20 years .
Now calculate it . We will clear , the loan in 1 6 years .
Fantastic , brother .
We were waiting for you . - Sister-in-law .
What 's the reason for that sparkling smile ? .
There 's good news . - What is it ? .
Ask your brother . Listen .
You never massage your hair with oil .
Have you seen the condition of your hair ? . It 's a complete mess .
Why are you getting angry with her , Mother ? .
Actually , that looks good on her .
Mother , ask him to keep quiet .
Why should he ? . Your brothers have spoiled you .
What have we done ? . - What have you brought for me ? .
Come . This is for you . And young man , this is for you . - Thank you .
Uncle , what is this ? . - That ! It 's for Priya . Was it necessary to ask ? .
See that , Mother . Gifts for the wife . But nothing for you . - Quiet .
Thank you . Mother , it 's just a cookbook .
Give . Give me this too .
Why are you getting angry ? .
Mother , if she reads the cookbook and cooks good food ..
.. it will benefit all of us .
So , this gift is for all of us . - Did I ask ? .
Hey , brother . So , what is the good news ? .
I got promoted . - Again ? . !
Yes . - So soon .
Yes . - There 's something better .
I have got a salary hike of 1 0,000 a month .
We have taken a loan for a period of 20 years for this house .
Now calculate it . We will clear the loan in 1 5 years .
What 's this ? . The pictures have still not been put up .
Mom , I sent the driller . Didn 't he come ? .
He did . There was such chaos .
Freshen up . Priya will explain it to you . - Okay .
Priya , what 's happened ? . - Take a bath . I 'll explain it to you .
You will have to talk to the society members .
There 's water leaking through the ceiling .
The stupid watchman must have forgotten to close the tap .
And the water must be seeping through .
I will talk to him tomorrow .
Your cookbook is very educational .
The recipes are just to die for .
And it has only non-veg items .
Fine , we will have a feast today .
Get ready , here comes Tarzan-boy . - Manu .
Go to page number 31 . The interesting stuff .
I can 't understand the head or tails of it .
Do you want me to do this ? .
I know . Why not start with a simple one ? .
Go to page number 44 . The easy one .
Do you know it by heart ? .
Show it to me . - Look .
Look , these small snacks aren 't satisfying at all .
You and I need a seven-course meal . - Shut up .
I will try all of this on you . - Fine , I will look for another one .
Okay .
Look at this one . This ..
Do people really do such things , Mannu ? . - Yes .
- Look at this . - Just a minute . I 'll be back .
Manu . What happened , Manu ? . - Careful . There 's glass .
You are bleeding . Yes , Manu .
The driller was saying that there 's industrial power here .
Industrial power . - And you should ..
That driller is a fool .
The fridge , T.V. and microwave are working , aren 't they ? . - Yes .
Then how can there be industrial power ? .
I know the bulb was a fake one . That 's why it exploded .
I will get it repaired tomorrow . Let 's leave that .
Listen to me . Listen . - Yes .
Look . - Tell me . - After all that discussion , I am feeling very hungry .
And I need something to eat quickly . - Today you 're fasting .
Fast ? . I don 't earn all that money to sleep on an empty stomach .
I want an entire feast today . Listen to me .
I am talking to you . - Fine . What would you like to have ? .
You know what I would like to have . I would like ..
- Leave me .
" Walking under the sky , we arrived at our home . "
" Our room , that 's covered with clouds .. "
" You will find it only in your dreams . "
" l have asked the stars to sparkle . "
" Call out my name once more . "
" Let your desires fly . "
" Let 's share our happiness . "
" Wait . "
" Walking under the sky , we arrived at our home . "
" Our room , that 's covered with clouds .. "
" You will find it only in your dreams . "
" l have asked the stars to sparkle . "
" Call out my name once more . "
" Let your desires fly . "
" Let 's share our happiness . "
" Wait . "
Divya . Where are you going ? .
Will you wear these clothes for the marriage ? .
Marriage ? . ! Who 's going for the marriage ? .
I am going to college . Today my results are coming out .
It 's no use . We know what 's going to happen .
Why are you wasting petrol and money ? .
In the last three years you haven 't passed a single subject .
And she won 't all her life . - Mother , you are just ..
Come here . Come here .
You know we all love you so much . - Are you taunting me ? .
Can 't you do a small thing for us ? . - What is it ? .
Just pass in any one subject . I will buy you any car you 'd like .
No . She won 't waste her brother 's money at all .
Okay , so as one unit , mother and son are against me .
What would I have done without my sisters-in-law ? .
Sister-in-law . - Yes .
What ? . - Give me Rs.500.
Of course . - My purse .
She 's your younger sister . Give her the money .
There 's only 200 . Will that do ? . - Give it back .
Thank you , sister-in-law .
You know why he is refusing to attend your friend 's marriage ? .
He is not feeling good . - He isn 't feeling good .
There are two beer bottles in the fridge .
You can check if you 'd like .
I can 't say anything else . - Come here . Hey , failure . Duffer .
Failure in eight subjects .
What is it ? .
The milk has curdled again .
Won 't I get a descent cup of tea in this house ? .
I got hurt on my face . I look like a drunkard .
Everyone will laugh at me in this condition .
I have sent the entire family .
There 's someone at the door . Have that file sent tomorrow .
Okay . Bye .
Coming .
Good morning , sir . Here 's my cheek .
You can give me a tight slap .
It 's such a nice cheek . Why should I slap it ? .
Actually , I invited you for lunch .
But a family wedding came up .
And my entire family left to attend the wedding .
And I am left alone in the house , without lunch .
That 's fine .
Do you have beer in the afternoon ? .
Only if I have company .
There 's a six-foot tall company . Come on .
We will have beer together . Come .
Sir , come in . I will switch off the microwave . - Fine .
Harry , come .
Harry .
Come in .
Why are you barking ? .
Harry .
Come in , Harry . Behave yourself .
I asked you to come in .
Come . Harry , be a good boy now .
Come on .
Come in . Come in .
What 's wrong with you , Harry ? .
What is the matter with you ? .
Come in now . Come , Harry .
Harry . Harry . Harry .
Sir . Sir , what 's wrong ? .
Sir .
My glasses , Manohar . My stick .
I 'll pick it up . Your glasses and stick . - Thank you .
Sir , what 's wrong ? . Harry . I will go get him . - No .
He cannot leave me .
Look . He is calling me .
Manohar , something scared him here .
His voice seemed very scared .
Anyway , I will take a rain-check on the beer today . Fine .
Some other day . - Fine .
Sorry . Harry . - I understand .
Harry . - Are you okay ? .
Yes , thank you .
Mother , look at how our house finally appears .
Something bad is happening in this house since we arrived .
The milk curdles everyday . The prayer room is still not ready .
There 's someone in this house other than my family .
Ghosts , ghouls , spectres or someone 's soul .
I have been promoted . - Wow .
I got a salary hike of 1 0,000 a month .
Now you calculate it .
We have taken a 20-year loan for this house .
But we will repay it back in 1 6 years .
Will you do something for me ? . - What ? .
For me , only once .. pass in at least one paper .
I 'll buy whichever vehicle you want .
Mohan . - Yes , Mother .
Chitra . What ? .
Oh my God . I have passed . I don 't believe it . I have passed .
It 's a miracle , brother . It 's a miracle . - What happened ? .
You 'll be amazed to know . - What happened ? .
I have passed in all my exams . - What ? .
And I have even broken my college record .
Everything in one go ! 69.73 % .
Oh my God . - Congratulations .
Congratulations won 't do .
One car for passing one paper .
I 've passed in 1 2 papers , brother . So you better be prepared .
Where are the others ? . - Attending the marriage .
The marriage . What was mama saying the other day ? .
Hello , sister-in-law . I have passed . Not just in one ..
.. but in all the exams .
.. but in all the papers .
Tell brother that I passed .
Can 't you wait for five minutes ? . Is it so important ? .
Okay , tell me .
Really ! Really !
Mannu . I 've been observing ..
Since you brought that cookbook ..
.. you have become very naughty .
There 's a time for everything .
That 's not it . - Then ? .
Priya , are you feeling fine ? . Do you feel nauseous at times ? .
No , why ? . You are just .. - I was just asking .
Priya , did you .. When did we get mother 's medical test done ? .
Eight to ten months earlier .
It 's been ten months . - Yes .
No , that 's not right . I will call Dr. Shinde tomorrow .
And take mother , sister-in-law and Divya along .
And get your medical test done as well .
Why are you being so concerned ? .
I just want to make sure that all the women in our family ..
.. are hale and hearty . - So sweet .
Sure , I will get it done .
K. D. ! Listen . Will you take care of things for two to three hours ? .
What 's wrong ? .
There 's good news . - What is it ? .
Priya is expecting . - Wonderful news .
Thanks . - Congratulations .
Take the entire day off . Have fun . I 'm there .
I will handle everything . - Sure .
Absolutely , sure . - Thanks .
Now leave . - Alright , see you .
All the best .
And listen .. - Yes .
Give my regards to Priya .
And bring sweets along .
Sir . - Who is it ? .
Sir , Manohar . - Manohar .
What is it ? . Why are you honking away ? .
Can I come with you in the lift ? .
Have you pressed the button , Manohar ? .
The stupid thing doesn 't work only for me . - What ? .
Nothing . - There 's something ..
I can smell wonderful sweets . Flowers too .
Some paper packets as well .
Manohar , what are you celebrating ? .
You are an amazing man , sir .
You are right , sir . I am going to be a father . - Congratulations .
So , why are you feeling so shy ? .
It 's something to be proud of . - Thank you .
I feel your new house is very lucky for all of you .
No . I mean , that day I met your elder brother in the car park .
He was saying that he got promoted .
Last night , Divya came home with sweets .
She said she passed with first-class results in her exams .
And now you are sharing good news .
So much good news so quickly .
The ' Vaast ' ( Feng Shui ) of your house is very good .
You are absolutely right . It is . It is very nice .
Where 's mother ? .
Divya .
Was it the interesting one ? .
Or the difficult one ? .
Shut up .
Actually , it 's the other one .
" Away from pondering eyes . "
" Keep it concealed . "
" Our love should never be jinxed . "
" Let 's pilfer the moon . "
" And keep it just for ourselves . "
" Don 't let the night know . "
" I 've brought happiness to ward off grievances . "
" Life seems like a celebration . "
" These small houses in these big cities . "
" How can they hold so much happiness ? . "
" Love , happiness , dreams . "
" l got everything I wished for . "
" These small houses in these big cities . "
" How can they hold so much happiness ? . "
" Love , happiness , dreams . "
" l got everything I wished for . "
" These days , a small child visits me in my dreams . "
" He tells me everything . "
" l invited him to come home soon . "
" Don 't be shy to share happiness . "
" It 's happiness all around . "
" I 've brought happiness to ward off grievances . "
" Life seems like a celebration . "
" These small houses in these big cities . "
" How can they hold so much happiness ? . "
" Love , happiness , dreams . "
" l got everything I wished for . "
" These small houses in these big cities . "
" How can they hold so much happiness ? . "
" Love , happiness , dreams . "
" l got everything I wished for . "
Priya . - Yes .
How much do we pay for the cable ? . - What ? .
How much do we pay for the cable every month ? . - Rs.200. Why ? .
If we don 't need it , why not disconnect it ? .
You want to disconnect the cable .
The last time I gave you a beating , you were five years old .
If you touch the cable , I will beat you again .
What 's for dinner ? . - You were saying something .
I didn 't hear it properly . About disconnecting something .
I was saying , I can shred the vegetables if you want .
You wanted to disconnect the cable . I heard it clearly . Why ? .
Yes , I did . I work hard to earn money .
No one is watching T.V.
If I can save Rs.200 , I can repay my loan faster .
Fine . If you can repay the house loan by saving Rs.200 ..
.. we don 't want this house , but we do want the cable .
We didn 't switch on the T.V. because you were at home this afternoon .
And you want to disconnect the cable .
Come on , we will watch T.V. right now .
Come on . - Yes , go .
You know , we watch a new T.V. programme these days .
'Sab Khairiyat ' ( Everything 's fine ) .
It 's absolutely different from those daily soap operas .
It also has spectres . It 's really interesting .
Come quickly , Mummy .
Yes , let 's watch what 's happening .
We missed the past few episodes .
She was pregnant in the last episode .
What happened ? .
Why do bad things happen to good guys ? .
She had such faith in Lord Ganesha .
And the bad ones are always depicted well .
Mummy , it 's just a programme . Why are you so tense ? .
I kept something in the kitchen .
Keep it in the fridge . Go . - Fine .
Come back soon .
You are sneaking a peek and feel ashamed to watch the show with us .
Come out , come on out .
No one will say anything . - No , Priya . listen to me ..
Mannu , are you fine ? . What 's wrong with you ? .
Hello . Hello !
Priya .
Priya . Priya . What 's wrong ? .
Priya . What happened ? . Priya . Priya .
Priya . Priya . Listen to me . - Priya ..
Sister-in-law . - Priya .
Quickly call the ambulance . - Mother .
Priya . - What happened to her ? .
How did this accident occur ? .
I don 't know how she slipped down the stairs .
She should take good care of herself .
I don 't know how this accident occur .. Doctor , please do something .
I cannot live without her . If anything happens to her ..
.. I don 't know what I will do .
I beg you to tell me . Will my wife survive ? .
I will give you anything you want . Money , wealth ..
I will give you everything .
Doctor , I can 't stay without her .
Tell me . Doctor , why don 't you say anything ? .
Why are you quiet ? .
Your silence is scaring me .
Doctor , please tell me .
Doctor , please . Will my wife survive ? .
Come on , man . Come on .
Will my wife be alive ? .
Doctor , how is Priya ? . - I don 't know what to say .
What do you mean ? . She 's been here for 24 hours .
If you still don 't say anything , then ..
Manoj , you are like a family member .
I won 't lie to you . We are trying our best .
But she 's still critical and her condition hasn 't improved .
But I will do my best .
Doctor , the patient is in serious condition .
Manoj , what did the doctor say ? . - Nothing , Mother .
Nothing ! What do you mean by nothing ? .
She 's been here for 24 hours , and still .. - I don 't know , Mother .
But it 's not good news . - Oh God .
What will we tell Mannu ? . - No ..
I don 't understand . If the doctor cannot tell us , then who can ? .
Everything will be fine . - I am scared .
I assure you , everything will be fine . - How can you say that ? .
I know everything will be fine . Try to calm down .
Excuse me , can I switch on the T.V. ? .
Darn it .
Excuse me , doesn 't this T.V. work ? .
No , sir . It 's not been working for the past one week .
Oh god .
Watchman ! Watchman !
Come with me . - What are you doing , sir ? . Sir .
Sir . - How is madam ? .
Fine . - Sir , the Lord will look after her .
Fine . - Sir , what did the doctor say ? .
Sir , why aren 't you telling me ? .
Quiet ! Quiet !
Tell me , doctor . Will my wife survive ? .
Doctor , please tell me . Why don 't you say something ? .
Will my wife survive ? .
I am so sorry .
Sometimes all the efforts of the doctor cannot change destiny .
As a doctor , I did my best .
I tried my level best . But I couldn 't save your child .
But your wife , she 's absolutely alright .
Don 't worry .
We 'll discharge her till tomorrow .
I am so sorry . - No .
I should have been careful , Mannu .
A small mistake . I know how much you love children .
What happened ? . It wasn 't anything grave .
You are absolutely alright .
If anything had happened to you , then I .. couldn 't have survived .
There 's just one punishment for this .
We will together bear 1 00 children .
Manu . - I love you , Priya .
I am sorry . - It 's okay . It 's okay .
I am very sorry , Manohar .
Thank you , Doctor . Thank you .
Is there anything I can do for you ? .
I know you are very happy .
But I didn 't know what had happened to her in the last 24 hours .
I conducted every test .
But the results of every test were contradictory .
And she 's going to be discharged within an hour .
And I haven 't given her a small pill .
If you want to say thank you ..
.. there 's a small temple in the compound .
Go and break a coconut there . - Okay .
And if you want to do something for me , then get me these medicines .
I need to give them to Priya . - Sure .
Thanks , Doctor . - Okay .
I 'll be back . Just a minute .
Sir , change .
Excuse me , may I have a look at the paper ? . - Yes , sure .
Thank you .
Where are you going ? .
Is this the EYE T.V. studios ? . - Yes .
Is ' Sab Khaiyriyat ' shot here ? . - Yes .
Are the writer , producer and director of this programme here ? .
Who are you ? . - I am a businessman ..
.. and I want to sponsor this programme . - Okay .
Oh , please come in .
Come . Come in .
Okays , sir .
Greetings . Welcome back to ' Sab Khairiyat . '
I am Roshan Abbas , and we are still discussing the same topic ..
No , I am not talking about this .
I am talking about the ' Sab Khairiyat ' that 's telecasted ..
.. everyday at 1 o 'clock in the afternoon on EYE T.V.
This is the shooting of ' Sab Khairiyat . '
Wait here . I will call the director .
The topic that we are going to discuss here today ..
.. will entertain the people ..
According to Mr. Sharma , everything is fine at home when ..
Hello .
Hello , excuse me . I need ..
Love soon turns into a quarrel ..
We want the answer of this quarrel right now .
He 's successful in winning the first phase of ' Sab Khairiyat'
Till when will the men stay quiet ? . Let 's start the buzzer round .
Hello . - Hello , Mother it 's Manohar speaking .
Yes , Mannu . What is it ? . - How is Priya ? .
Priya ? . She 's fine . She 's sleeping .
Have the children returned from school ? .
Children ? . ! No , they still haven 't .
Mannu , you are disturbing me .
I am at a very interesting part of the programme .
Is it something important ? . Or else call me later .
After half an hour . - Mother . Just a minute .
Which programme are you watching ? . - My favourite one . ' Sab Khairiyat ' !
God ! Oh God !
Mannu , you have known me for so many years .
When did you notice this written on my forehead ? .
Silly ! Fool ! Stupid !
No , I don 't know whether you are a fool , or am I ? .
But Shivam , I do know that I lost my child . - I know .
My wife has nearly escaped death .
Please . I am serious .
I think my whole family is in danger .
Look . I am an educated man .
I could have taken some priest home ..
.. and held some prayers .
But no . I thought , my good friend is a police officer .
If I seek his help , he will give me a solution .
But if you want to laugh about it , then that 's fine .
Enjoy your joke , brother .
Hey , Mannu . Sorry . Sorry .
Listen to me . - It 's not a joke , Shiva . It 's not a joke .
I am sorry . But if you tell anyone about this , they 'll laugh .
Fair enough . - Anyways , now that you have approached me ..
Don 't worry , I will solve the problem .
At what time is the programme telecasted ? . - 1 o 'clock .
They don 't even let us watch the programme .
Someone is always ringing the bell .
Go see who it is , Priya . - You go .
" Everyone is happy as everything is alright . "
" Friends , everything is alright . "
What is it ? . Why do you come home whenever you want ? .
There 's no food at home . Go away . - Are you done ? .
Yes . - Now , meet him .
Hi , Shiva . - Hi .
I 'm so sorry . I thought it 'd be him alone .
Mummy , look who has come ? . - Who is it ? .
Mom . Shiva . - Shiva . After so many days .
Hello , Aunt . - You didn 't even come for the house warming .
I think you have forgotten us .
No Aunt , I haven 't forgotten at all .
But I don 't get any time outside of my responsibilities .
Otherwise why would I have come today ? .
Just a minute . Move aside ..
And how is Manoj ? . Are the children fine ? . - Yes .
They are absolutely fine .
I am so sorry . It 's the same thing at my house .
At least you opened the door .
My mother doesn 't even open the door ..
.. while watching her favourite programme .
Manu , we 'll talk later . Let us watch first .
Not here . Sit here . - Okay .
Take a seat . It 's very interesting . - Yes . - Have a seat .
Mannu , I will serve food during the break . - Fine .
Can you watch T.V. ? . - Yes .
Keep watching .
You 're back . - Eeshwar , that 's Gayatri , my wife , .
Hello .
See , I told you so . That 's you . That 's you .
Come in .
Hello , Mother . How are you ? . - Bless you , son .
How are you ? . - I 'm fine . Just a minute .
Excuse me .
Hello . Yes , Mr. Madan , how are you ? .
Why did you call ? .
What ? .
When did this happen ? .
In the hospital . Which one ? .
But is she fine ? .
Wait for me . I 'll be there soon .
What happened ? .
The cylinder at my home exploded .
Shiva . Come with me . Hurry up .
What are you doing , Mannu ? .
Shiva , listen to me .
Stop freaking out and behaving like a psycho . - Listen to me !
Call him right now . - But why ? .
Just because you saw something on television ..
Shiva . - What the ..
It 's a matter of life and death . - Okay .
I am calling .
Call home , and tell Sheila to get out of the house right now .
Just a minute . I 'm doing it .
The network 's busy . - God darn it .
The stupid network .
Oh my God .
Come on , come on .
Relax , Mannu .
Hello . - Sheila ! She 's on the line .
Ask her to get out of the house right now . - Just a minute .
Let me talk to her . Sheila , it 's me .
What are you doing ? .
Why ? . What 's wrong ? .
Leave everything , and get out of the house . Right now .
Sheila . It got disconnected . - Oh God , come with me .
Come on , fast . There 's no time .
Mother , I 'm leaving . - Mannu , have something to eat .
Where are you going ? .
Where are they going ? .
What has happened ? .
Why is this happening with me ? .
Relax , everything will be fine .
She cannot even smell anything .
Sheila . Are you fine ? . - What 's wrong ? .
Stay here . I will be back .
Kitchen . - Oh God !
I just can 't believe this Mannu . It 's just so bizarre .
I still can 't believe it , Manu . How can this happen ? .
You were laughing at me when I was telling you .
Now we both are entrapped in this .
What do you mean by " we " ? . - I was leading a normal life ..
.. with my wife and child . How can I be entrapped in this story ? .
If anything happens to them , Mannu .. - Shiva .
I 'm not doing all of this .
I don 't know how this is happening .
I am stuck in this on my own . I don 't know what to do .
What do you mean ? . Just vacate that house .
What are you thinking ? . What are you still waiting for ? . Get out now .
Shiva . I cannot vacate that house .
Why ? . Why cannot you vacate it ? . What do you mean ? .
Shiva , listen to me .
My house is the only place where the programme telecasts .
If we hadn 't seen it at the right time ..
Sister-in-law 's life was in danger .
We couldn 't have saved her .
If I vacate that house , I will never get to know ..
.. what 's going on in that programme .
And if something bad is going to happen ..
.. I won 't be able to save my family from it , Shiva .
And you thought I was joking .
I am entrapped in it as well , Mannu .
But Mannu .. You are absolutely right , Mannu .
Don 't go out of that house at all .
And first of all , it 's very important for you to stay in that house .
And don 't tell your family about this ..
.. or else they will ask you to vacate the house .
And Mannu , most importantly ..
.. please ask your family to pay close attention ..
.. to the inspector 's duties .
Or else , they might just side-track it ..
.. and not pay close attention . And the inspector ..
You understand what I am ..
Now , you understand what I am going through .
Harry . What 's wrong ? .
What , Harry ? . Is there someone , Harry ? .
Hello , is anyone there ? .
Anyone there ? . Harry .
Careful . Stop .
Sir , what 's wrong ? .
Sir . - Manohar .
Yes sir , just a minute . - Son .
Thank you . - Are you okay ? .
Yes , but something happened to Harry .
He must have spotted a cat or something .
He just ran away .
Sir , come here . Take a seat . I will look for him .
Harry .
Harry . What are you doing there ? .
Harry , come here .
Harry . Come here , boy .
Good boy . Come here .
Come on .
Priya ! Priya ! What happened ? . - What ? . Nothing .
Why do you get so hyper ? . - No , I thought something happened .
Nothing happened .
I don 't know why , but you have been behaving strangely these days .
That 's not it . I felt like coming to the kitchen ..
.. and giving you a helping hand . - Really .
Yes . Because I 've heard that if husband and ..
.. wife work together in the kitchen ..
.. the intimacy between them increases .
You brought a cookbook earlier .
And now you are talking about psychology .
Forget it . So what 's the latest with you ? .
Do you still watch that programme on T.V. , ' Sab Khairiyat ' ? .
What happened in today 's episode ? .
You are addicted as well , right ? .
You got hitched as well , right ? .
And you used to mock us .
Now you call from the office to ask what happened on the show .
When you come to the kitchen you ask , " What happened on the show ? . "
But you won 't believe what happened on the show today .
Amazing . An amazing thing happened on the show today .
Why ? . What happened ? .
The neighbour . - Yes .
His dog . - Yes .
He goes into the garden and starts digging .
Then ? . - He keeps digging and digging .
Then what ? . - He finds something there .
What ? . - That 's what I would like to know myself .
But before they could show anything , it ended .
I am just fed up .
Sir , some people want an invitation to the political meeting .
You asked me to remind you . - Yes . Go .
Hello !
Yes , Kalsekar . - I will call you . I will call you later . Okay .
You have reminded me . Now leave .
Yes ! Sir . - Get back to your work .
Shiva . Shiva . Shiva . - Manu , you are so late .
Where were you ? . You said there 's something urgent .
Tell me what happened in yesterday 's episode .
Was I transferred ? . - Take a look .
What is this ? .
This is the tele-serial family .
Where did you find this ? .
Shiva , this was buried in the ground outside my house .
And look , there 's a calendar in this picture .
And the date is June 1 977 .
Shiva , this means this picture is 30 years old .
But even today these people can be seen on the show on my T.V ..
.. at the same age .
How .. how is this happening , Manohar ? .
What shall we do ? . - Shiva , I don 't know .
Dr. Shinde . - What ? .
Shiva , some days ago I saw an interview on television .
Dr. Shinde was doing extensive research ..
.. about ghosts , spectres and the paranormal .
Shiva , he made a lot of sense . - Let 's go now .
And tell him about everything . Come . Come .
No , Shiva . We cannot tell him everything . - Why ? .
Dr. Shinde is also my family doctor .
He operated on mom 's leg some years ago .
If I tell Dr. Shinde everything , he will instantly call home .
And tell mom everything . And there will be a huge confusion .
Shiva . Do you have normal clothes , other than this uniform ? .
Dr. Shinde . - Manohar . Come in .
How is Priya ? . - She 's absolutely fine .
And Shushma ? . - Mom is fine as well .
Are you feeling sick ? . - It 's nothing like that .
I needed a small favour . That 's why I troubled you .
Please come . Come . - Sorry I came without an appointment .
It 's alright .
This is my friend , Shiva .
Hello , Doctor . - Hi .
He 's a writer . And he 's writing something about ghosts ..
.. and paranormal activities .
He was stuck on something , and I thought about you .
So , what do you want to ask ? .
Actually Doctor , when I was writing my story ..
.. I read a story on the lnternet .. - I am sorry .
What will you have ? . Tea , coffee ? . - Tea .
Tea will be fine . - Okay .
I get it now .
There 's a family in Delhi . They watch a T.V. programme , ..
.. which is a replica of themselves .
I completely get it now .
Tell me one thing , Shiva .
Do you believe in the paranormal ? .
I mean , is there a possibility that lost souls , ghosts could exist ? .
Well .. One can 't clearly say that they don 't exist .
But I personally don 't .. - Fair enough .
Tell me one thing , which is the most complicated machine in the world ? .
There are so many of them , Doctor .
The rocket , the satellite , the computer .. - No. it 's the human body .
There 's nothing more complicated than the human body .
And a doctor will know that the best .
I mean , if we say that a lost soul has entered ..
.. something complicated like the human body ..
.. everyone will agree to it .
But it has entered a machine like the television .
No one is ready to believe that .
Forget that . Let us try to find out why the souls would try to do that .
Shiva , the lost souls need a medium to contact the real world .
The wandering souls need a medium to contact the real world .
So , why not the television ? .
Get one thing straight , Shiva .
Humans are not the only ones who change . Souls do too .
Doctor , let us assume that the ghosts and souls ..
.. can contact us through television .
But the question is why are they trying to contact us ? .
They have a motive . There 's a goal they want to achieve .
Something that 's left unfinished .
And they want to return to this world to finish it .
If anyone can achieve their goal ..
.. their souls will find solace .
And the programme won 't be telecast anymore .
You can say , the house where it 's telecasted ..
.. must be related to that place .
Shiva , listen to me .
All the people I saw on that T.V. show are all dead . That 's clear .
And like Dr. Shinde is saying , they want to say something ..
.. through the show .
And maybe that 's why we have found that album .
Shiva , I feel there 's something in the album that we 're missing .
We should check the album again .
Where 's the album ? . - In the car .
Just a minute . - What ? .
Just a minute . - Turn it back .
What is it ? . - Hold on .
I think we missed a photograph .
Look . There 's something below .. - Just a minute .
Carefully .
Shiva , do you see this man ? . - What ? .
Until now , I have seen everyone on the T.V. show except for this one .
Mannu . - Yes .
The calendar in the photograph shows the year 1 977 .
This means they were alive until June ' 77 .
That means they must have died after that .
So we have to check the papers after that month . Remember that .
'75 ! ' 77 !
Shiva .
Shiva . Check this out .
The younger sister in the television show .. - Yes .
She was a news reporter .
She and her eight family members were massacred with a hammer .
The children were not spared either .
And their address , 1 3B , Chabra Village .. Kailash Nagar .
What 's wrong , Mannu ? .
Shiva . - What ? .
The address of their house and my address are the same .
The number of their house is 1 3 , and I am on the 1 3th floor .
That means my apartment was built after demolishing their bungalow .
Gayatri , bring the vermillion and sandalwood .
Let me anoint it . - Yes .
Why just anoint it ? . Why not hold prayers ? . - Yes .
Do you know how expensive this television is ? .
Let me get one thing clear .
Only one person will touch this television .
I will show everyone how to switch it on and off .
And the children will not touch it .
This will look nice . - What are you doing ? .
Let it be . It will look good . - Mother ..
We don 't need your approval for everything .
Please . - Keep it there . - Fine .
Why are you still standing there ? .
Switch it on , so we can see something .
Be patient , Mother . Patience . I will .
Mohan . Mohan . Is it done ? . - Yes , brother . I finished .
Switch on the booster . I will turn the antenna .
Let me know when you get a signal .
Can you see anything ? .
Can you see anything ? . - No .
No , keep turning it .
Now . - Now .
There 's nothing . - Nothing can be seen .
Wait ! Wait ! I can see it .
No , we lost it . Ask him to turn it back .
Mohan . - Yes .
Turn it back . - Okay .
I got it . Okay , very good ! - That 's it .
We 've got a signal . - Is it clear ? .
It 's clear , absolutely clear .
Tightly tie the antenna over there . - Okay , brother .
What are you two doing there ? . - Nothing .
Go inside . The television is on .
Yes , Uncle .
Quickly hide it here .
Their sister , Chitra . That reads news on television .
The brothers have brought a new television to see her .
Today 's programme .
At 7 : 30 , the yoga programme , Yogmala . At 8 o 'clock ..
Wow . Mother , the television is so clear . - Yes .
Just a minute . - What are you doing ? .
Just a minute . I am cleaning it .
Go and call Ashok . - Yes .
He would like to see his brother as well .
My sister is looking so nice . - You move from there .
Just a minute . I am going .
Today in Rajasthan .. - Look . - Is the signal clear ? . - Yes .
Ganesh , call the neighbours . They can see your sister as well . - Fine .
Call them .
Laxmi , Gayatri . Spread a mat here for the neighbours to sit . Go .
Carefully , Ashok . Carefully .
We have brought a gift for you .
Do you know what the gift is ? .
Careful .
You will be very happy to see it .
Do you know what it is ? .
Look , we have arrived . - News .
Look , brother . The television .
Ashok .
Son , get up . Ashok .
Come , sit up . Sit up .
Son , just a minute .
Look , Chitra . Chitra . Look .
Minister of Maharashtra , Vasant Patil ..
You did recognise your sister .
You wouldn 't have recognized your father so soon .
What happened ? .
Sit . Sit .
Come in . Come in . - Come .
Some people can sit on the sofa .
And others on the floor . - Come .
What happened , brother ? .
Take him in the room . Take him away .
Take him in the room .
Stop it !
He never saw outsiders before today .
All the new faces scared him .
Move . Move back . Why are you crowding this place ? .
Dont you have any better work to do ? . What 's all this ? . Move back .
Who called me ? . - This man , sir .
Who are you ? . - Ram Charan , a High Court advocate .
How do you know this family ? . - Family friend .
I was engaged at the younger daughter , Chitra .
I brought the sample for the wedding invitation .
When I went inside .. I was scared , sir .
Come .
Hey .
Look here .
Hey , throw down the hammer .
Thrown it down , or else ..
Catch him .
Take him away .
Tie him up !
Pull him !
Desai .
Desai . - Yes , sir .
Yes , sir . - Call the ambulance . Call the obituary .
Call the forensics . Call everyone .
Inform headquarters as well .
This is a huge massacre . There are eight corpses here . - Yes , sir .
Desai . - Yes , sir .
Did you ask around ? . - Yes , sir . I did .
Does anyone know anything ? . - There are two people , sir .
Call them . - Yes , sir .
Come here . - Yes .
What 's your name ? . - Noor Mohammad .
I live in the room next door . I am scared of these incidents ..
Answer only what I ask you . - Yes , sir .
When did you find out about what happened in this house ? .
Right now . - Didn 't you hear anything last night ? .
No suspicious character ? . - No , sir .
No screaming nor yelling ? . - No , sir . It was nothing like that .
It 's altogether a different situation .
A ghost is responsible for this massacre . Ghost .
Really ? . You seem to know a lot .
I know more . The daughter of this house . Chitra ..
The one that read news on television .
She was very good looking , like a movie star .
He fell for her after seeing her on television .
Who is he ? . - The one that follows him . And misbehaves as well .
That day , on the day of engagement ..
.. he came here , barged inside the house .
He created such a racket . No one could do anything .
Her brother 's tried to reason with him .
But he wasn 't ready to listen . He threatened everyone .
If they don 't get their sister married to him ..
.. he will kill the entire family .
Will you recognise that boy ? . - Yes !
He 's not alive . He died a week ago .
On the engagement day , he created a ruckus ..
.. and on the same day , he cut his nerves . And died .
Can I tell you one more thing , sir ? . - What ? .
That boy 's soul has entered the madman 's body ..
.. and he is taking revenge .
This house is an unlucky one .
Have you noticed the number ? . Thirteen .
It can only be ghosts . There was just one .
Now , there will be eight more .
Eight people were massacred in this house .
But you didn 't hear or see anything .
But you did see the ghost . - Yes , sir .
You think I am a fool . - Yes , sir .
Get lost .
You send such fools for questioning .
Who else is it ? . - Hey , come forward .
This man ..
Did you see a ghost as well ? .
There are no ghosts , sir .
That madman has done everything .
They purchased a new television yesterday .
We came here to watch it as well .
But that madman created a ruckus . And broke everything .
And yelled at everyone .
And then we realised that he 's mad .
He had to be locked in the room , sir .
And because of his madness , he has committed this massacre .
Desai . - Yes .
Go along with him . And the people .. - Yes .
.. that came to watch T.V.
Bring them all to the police station . - Get that ? .
Yes . - And bring the advocate along as well .
Of course , sir . - And listen .
And the girl that died . Chitra .
Find the person that stopped her engagement ..
.. and committed suicide . - Yes , sir .
I want all these details on my table by morning .
He was arrested . But the lawyer that defended his case was Ram Charan .
Do you know who Ram Charan is ? . - Who ? .
Chitra 's fiancé . Chitra and he were engaged .
Chitra . Chitra .
What are you doing ? . - Chitra .
Who are you ? . Who are you ? . - Chitra . Chitra .
Don 't call our Chitra . She 's getting engaged .
Stop this engagement , please stop this engagement .
Who are you ? . What do you mean stop the engagement ? .
Chitra . Chitra . - Who is this man ? .
Chitra . Chitra . - Quiet .
I love Chitra . I love Chitra . - Quiet .
I see her on television everyday . - Quiet .
I see her on television .
Thousands of people watch our sister everyday .
So , will everyone get married to her ? .
I will take good care of her . I will take good care of her .
Get lost from here !
Chitra . Chitra . - Get out .
I have been trying to talk to you . But you don 't seem to understand .
I will kill you . I will kill the entire family .
Get lost . - Where did he come from ? . Chitra .
That boy committed suicide . Because he couldn 't marry Chitra .
Oh God , this is getting darn confusing , Manu .
I cannot understand anything .
Manu . - Yes .
Manu . - Yes , tell me .
Remember that day when I came home ? . - Yes .
An inspector came home that day . Remember ? .
Yes , the cylinder blast episode .
Do you know what his name was ? .
What ? . - Eeshwar Ghandre .
What ? . - Look at this .
He was the office investigating That case .
And strangely , he committed suicide in that very house .
He hung himself to death .
Strange .
There 's only one person that seems to be alive in all of this .
And that 's lawyer Ram Charan .
If we meet him and question him , we can find some information .
You are right . You are right , Manu .
What 's this nonsense ? . Switch it off .
What happened , again ? . - This remote . - It had to stop working now .
Mummy , I can 't change it .
I cannot watch this . I can 't bear it .
I hate this violence .
Sister in law .
He 's called me in the office . - Okay , sir . - You all leave there ..
.. I have to meet the judge regarding recess . - Yes , sir .
Sir , excuse me . Advocate Ram Charan . - Yes .
My name is Manoharan . - Shiva .
Sub-inspector Shiva . I talked to you on the phone .
Tell me , what can I do for you ? .
Sir , we wanted to talk to you privately ..
.. about this newspaper article .
Tell me , what do you want to know ? .
Why Ashok did such a thing ? .
Not allowing him to watch T.V. can 't be a justification .
Ashok cannot commit murder .
I have known that family for years .
Ashok loved Chitra immensely .
It was someone else .
He committed the murder , and left the hammer right there .
Yes . Ashok hugged everyone 's body and was weeping .
And that 's why he had bloodspots on him .
I saw it myself . He was angry with the television .
I think he considered the television responsible for it .
And he took the hammer and started breaking the television .
And that 's how the hammer had his fingerprints .
I tried my best to save him in court . But I lost .
Sir , where is Ashok now ? .
Yes . Advocate Ram Charan called me .
Is Ashok here ? . - Yes , he has been here for years .
But we recently shifted him to a different cell .
Solitary confinement . - Why , Doctor ? .
For 30 years he has been a model patient .
As a part of therapy , we let the patients watch television ..
.. for an hour everyday .
That day , Feb 21 st ..
He became very violent while watching television .
God knows what he saw on television ..
.. but he was very disturbed .
After that , he had self-inflicted wounds .
He would draw squares , boxes and similar ..
.. figures on the wall with his blood .
We couldn 't control him .
That 's why , you know .. - Doctor , can we meet Ashok ? .
Ashok . Ashok .
Leave it . Let go of my hand .
Leave it .
Move back , Manu .
Are you fine ? . - No .
It 's Priya . Yes , Priya .
Where are you ? . When are you coming home ? .
I will be there within 1 0 to 20 minutes .
Ask her what happened in today 's episode .
Priya , just a minute .
What happened in today 's episode ? .
I told you , and you were mocking me .
And now you 're inquiring about the episode .
Put it on speakerphone . - Yes .
I just called to tell you that I 've laid the food on the table ..
Priya , leave all of that aside .
Just tell me what happened in today 's episode .
It was such a gruesome scene , we couldn 't see it .
What happened ? .
A man entered the house with a big hammer and killed everyone .
Priya . - Yes .
Did they show who the killer was ? . - No .
Like everyday , it ended abruptly .
That means we will only find out tomorrow who 's behind it .
Today is Friday . They will show it on Monday .
Priya , listen to me . Listen carefully . - What is it ? .
Is brother at home ? . - I think so .
Priya , lock all the doors and windows of the house . - Why ? .
No matter what happens , whoever it is , no matter what he says ..
.. don 't open the doors and windows .
But what 's wrong ? . - Listen to me .
When I come home , I will ring the bell thrice .
Open the door only then .
You are trying to scare me , right ? . - Please don 't argue with me .
Just do as I say , Priya . Please .
Shiva . Shiva , someone 's going to come to my home ..
.. and murder everyone .
You go home . I will go to the police station ..
.. and come back with the force .
We will surround the entire building .
I will station one man at every floor .
Let 's see who it is .
Hello .
Who is it ? . - Watchman .
Who is it ? .
Stop . Hello , wait . Stop .
Who are you ? . Stop .
Stop right there .
Stop . Watchman .
Hey .
Watchman , come quickly .
What 's happening ? .
Hey !
No Priya , don 't open the door
Priya , don 't open the door .
Manohar , what happened ? . - Nothing .
Was it a bad dream ? . - Nothing , go back to sleep .
Tell me , Mannu , tell me .
Priya .. - Seems like you saw a ghost .
Mannu . Mannu , what 's wrong ? .
It 's me , Priya . Why are you so scared ? .
Oh God , was it a bad dream ? .
" Everything is alright . "
" There 's happiness all around . Everything is alright . "
" Friends , Everything is alright here . "
" Everything is alright . "
Come on . Come on .
Come on . Who is it ? .
Come on . Show me .
Show me .
Manohar , I can 't understand anything you are saying .
My family can be in danger because of me .
What danger ? . - I know my family can be in danger ..
.. because of my mental state .
I am going to murder my entire family .
Do you get that ? . - What are you saying ? .
How do I explain it to you ? .
I see bad dreams . Not just in the night , but during days as well .
I don 't know what 's true and what 's not .
Whom should I believe , and whom should I not ? .
I .. Doctor , there are only two ways to avert this .
Firstly , lock me up in a place from where I cannot escape .
Or else , the other option is that you kill me .
What nonsense ? . - No , look . I am being practical .
Listen to me . I am not being emotional .
And if anything happens to my family because of me , I will die as it is .
And Doctor , before I do anything , just kill me . Just kill me .
This is nonsense . Calm down .
No , you calm down . Shiva , try to explain it to him .
Mannu , relax . - Just a second , calm down . Calm down .
I will talk to him . - Okay .
Doctor , I have an idea . - What ? .
Let 's send his family far away without telling him .
Then he wouldn 't be able to do anything , even if he wants to .
Because he just won 't know where they are .
Shiva . - What are you thinking about ? .
Shiva , hold that thought .
It 's a really good idea . It 's a really good idea .
Okay . - Listen to me .
.. and don 't tell me about it ? .
But at this time , how will I get all the plane tickets ? .
Doctor , on the lnternet . Do you have lnternet connection ? . - Yes .
I 'll do it . - He 's right .
Look , log onto the lnternet , book the tickets .
And take my family . No , go to my home ..
.. and take them to a place where I can 't find them .
I shouldn 't know where they are and so shouldn 't he .
And one more thing . Tell Priya and my entire family ..
Mannu , catch your breath .
I am really sorry . - Relax Manu , cool down .
Ask Priya to call me . I will explain everything to her .
But Doctor , we don 't have the time .
We have to move . We have to act right now .
Let 's go now . Please , please . - Okay , lets go .
Look Shiva , take me to that room and close all the doors and windows .
No matter what I do , or say .
Though I might be dying , don 't open the door .
Get that ? . - Relax , Manu .
Here . Keep the house keys . And carefully . Bye . - Bye .
Shiva , open the door , open it please .
Shiva . - What 's wrong , Manu ? .
Shiva , open the door . I have understood everything .
What did you understand ? .
The television programme that ..
.. I saw today had two hammers .
Different ones .
What are you saying , Manu ? .
There were two different people on the show today , Shiva .
Manu , I don 't understand anything . Go back to sleep .
Open the door . I will explain it to you .
Open the door , please .
Manu , I won 't open the door before morning . Go back to sleep .
Fine , don 't open the door . Just listen to me carefully .
In the climax that I saw today there were two different hammers .
This means there were two different people !
The one that killed the entire family has a normal hammer .
You know , the one that 's used for pulling out nails as well .
And the other one was mine . I was carrying the bigger hammer .
And there was a red tape on the handle .
Like a sledge hammer .
Shiva , that hammer is right here . It was in front of me outside .
Shiva , that could mean only one thing .
Someone 's going to go to my house ..
.. and my family is in danger .
In the television show I reached home late .
That 's why he killed my family .
If I want to save my family , then I will have to reach on time .
Please Shiva , open the door . I beg of you , open the door .
Shiva , for God sakes open the door . Open the door , Shiva . - Okay .
Okay , Mannu . - Please , hurry up . Please .
Thank God . I don 't have time .
Shiva , open the door . What are you doing ? .
No Manu , no . I won 't open the door , Manu .
Shiva . - I will open the door only in the morning .
If I have to kill you to save your family , then I will do that as well .
You get that straight .
So just shut up and sleep , Manu .
Shiva , open the door . Please listen to me , and open the door .
Man . - Manu .
Let me go . Open the door , Shiva .
Manu ! - Oh , god damn it !
Shiva , please open the door . Let me go .
Please , let me go . - Manu .
You fool . - Shiva ! - You idiot .
Manu . Manu . Manu .
Manu !
Where is he ? .
What 's wrong with him these days ? .
Manu .
Hi , Priya . - Uncle , it 's so late in the night .
Manu is not at home . - I know he 's at my house .
Are you fine .. ? . - He has asked me to give you this .
I don 't understand . What is this ? .
Priya , these are air-tickets .
All of you have to leave for Delhi by the morning 7 o 'clock flight .
What ? . But why ? . - Don 't worry .
Call Manohar . He will tell you everything .
Fine . Uncle , come in . Please .
I am tired of climbing up 1 3 floors . - I am so sorry .
It 's a power cut . Can I get you some water ? .
Yes , and get me a black coffee without sugar . - Sure , take a seat .
I 'll get it .
Priya , where 's the bathroom ? . - In front of you .
I will bring the candle . It 's - okay . I will find it .
The electricity has come .
The main headlines .
Thirty years ago , television news reporter , Chitra , and her family ..
.. which also included children , were massacred with a hammer .
The police have taken Chitra 's elder brother into custody .
And he 's a mental patient .
He has been accused of committing all the murders .
A madman has committed this murder .
But it wasn 't my brother . It was you !
Your foolish brother didn 't value his life .
That 's why he committed suicide .
Just because a girl refused to marry him ..
But how are we responsible for it ? .
If you loved your brother so much , and you were so sad about his death ..
.. you should have committed suicide yourself .
Sairam . Sairam .
What did you do ? .
Chitra ! - Hey , why are you barging in ? . - Throw him out !
.. doesn 't have a right to live .
Find out who the boy was that came here ..
.. and created an uproar . - Yes , sir .
Doctor , I am sorry to hear about your brother 's death .
I 'll be with you in a minute . - Okay .
Why did you kill us ? .
If you would have been punished for your deeds ..
.. it might have calmed our fury .
But you accused my brother of everything ..
.. who could never commit a sin .
You proved him to be a murderer .
And left him to rot in the mental asylum .
That was wrong .
Better yet , you should have killed him along with us .
But you have punished him the worst .
And that 's wrong . It 's a crime .
We could have killed you if we wanted to .
But no . We want my brother to be acquitted of all accusations .
He should be set free .
And that 's why we will kill you right where you massacred us .
Today , our rage will finally be at peace .
And our souls will find solace .
You will be punished for your sins . - Punished .
How else can you punish me ? .
I lived without my brother for 30 years .
What was my brother 's fault ? .
Tell me , what was wrong with my brother ? .
I brought him up with much love and adoration .
I am proud of my brother .
My brother died because of you .
I won 't spare any of you .
I will .
I will kill you . I will kill you . I will kill you .
Uncle . Uncle .
Brother . - What is that noise ? .
Brother . - What 's going on ? . - Brother ..
Priya - why are you shouting ? .
Why did Priya shout ? . - Look , here .
Priya .. - What 's going on ? .
What happened ? .
Who is he ? .
Divya , take the children inside . Quickly .
Doctor . - What are you doing ? .
Doctor , what 's wrong ? .
Doctor , what 's wrong with you ? . Stop .
Doctor , listen to me . Throw down the hammer .
Carefully , brother .
Please try to understand .
Listen to my doctor .
Doctor !
No ! Doctor !
Don 't do it .
No !
Stop it . Manohar , just stop it .
Smile ! Smile ! Smile !
Thank you .
Come on , I am getting late .
Time to go to the office .
Mother . - The prayer is complete .
I asked him to make a prayer room . Instead , he made a temple .
Here .
Hello , baby . Looking nice .
Listen . Remember you have to go to the doctor today .
You have told me 1 00 times , I remember .
So what ? . Is it an easy thing ? .
Brother , how are you ? .
I 'll keep this right here .
You can ask for anything you want .
Shiva . I talked to the lawyer .
He was saying that all the papers are clear .
That means all the problems are solved .
Thanks to you . No , I really mean it .
Then say something else .
Like let 's meet in the evening , have a beer .
Fine . Don 't get too excited .
I 'll see you soon . Bye .
Dr. Shinde ? .
Hello . - Manohar . Surprised ? .
You know , if we die in this generation ..
.. and our souls want to communicate with the real world ..
.. we will not use the television , but mobile phones instead .
And is everything fine ? .
" Sexy . "
" These salacious eyes ask me to die for them . "
" These alluring eyes will make them fall for us . "
" Sexy . "
" These alluring eyes will make those lovers go mad . "
" These alluring eyes will make them fall for us . "
" Sexy . "
" These alluring eyes will make those lovers go mad . "
" Without you , I have no destination . "
" l cannot live without you . "
" l will die without you . "
" My evenings are incomplete without you . "
" We have to meet up . I 'm helpless in your love . "
" Oh sexy mama , won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Oh sexy mama . "
" Oh sexy mama , won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Oh sexy mama . "
" Oh sexy mama , won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Oh sexy mama . "
" Make me happy too . "
" Why don 't you meet me these days ? . "
" l am lost without you . "
" l am your soul . "
" We have to meet somewhere . "
" How can you live without me ? . "
" You will keep sighing without me . "
" What 's the problem ? . Come into my arms . "
" Oh sexy mama , won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Oh sexy mama . "
" Your sharp eyes .. - Sexy . "
" .. say .. - Sexy . "
" Come and ..
.. drink poison . - Sexy . "
" Come to me . "
" How will you live without me ? . "
" You 'll yearn for me . "
" What 's the problem ? . Come and embrace me . "
" Oh sexy mama , won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Oh sexy mama . "
" Oh sexy mama , won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Won 't you do the SAREGAMA ? . "
" Oh sexy mama . "
" Oh Sexy . "